makingmusicfun.net 2014-11-22

# Terms Of Use/Privacy Policy | MakingMusicFun.net

Terms of Use  
By accessing and using the MakingMusicFun.net (MMF!) website, you are agreeing to be legally bound by the terms and conditions of MMF! (Wave Music, LLC). If you do not agree, please do not use this site. 

MMF! is not responsible or liable for any infections or contaminations of your system, or delays, inaccuracies, errors, or omissions arising out of your use of this site or with respect to the information and materials contained on this site. The entire risk as to the quality, accuracy, adequacy, completeness, correctness and validity of any material rests with you.

MMF! links to third-party sites. These links are provided for your reference, and MMF! assumes no responsibility for any content made available at any third-party site.

All site design, text, printable material and code are property of MMF!, owner and operator of this website. You may use this site for educational and personal use.

All printable materials may be used and/or duplicated, provided that:   

> a) Materials are used for educational, non-commercial purposes  
>  b) No modifications to the materials are made  
>  c) Materials are not used in a manner that suggests endorsement by MMF!  
>  d) Materials are not used in a manner that infringes and/or violates any right of any third party, these terms, or any law. All resources included on this site are public domain in the United States except where noted. If you live outside the United States, you must determine if copyright laws for your country permit you to legally download these files.  
>  e) Materials may not be hosted on other websites without our written consent. To do so is a violation of section 512(f) of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). Any person who knowingly uploading and/or hosting copyrighted materials is infringing on Wave Music, LLC (MakingMusicFun.net) copyright, and may be subject to liability.  
>  f) All copyright and other proprietary notices are kept intact 

No commercial non-education use, resale, or exploitation of material from the site is permitted without the express written permission of MMF! (Wave Music, LLC).

All published music teacher directory content (image and text) becomes property of MMF!, and may be used to promote the teacher directory for the purpose of enhancing the value of this resource.

**Basically...**  
MakingMusicFun.net was created for teachers, students, and folks that love music. Print or read anything you like. Just don't charge people for the resources you find on our website, or put our stuff on your website. Thanks!

Privacy Policy  
MMF! (Wave Music, LLC) respects the privacy of each visitor, especially kids!

Website Tracking   
MMF! collects the following nonpersonal information to assess the value the resources offered:

> a) The name of the domain from which visitors access the internet  
>  b) The date and time that visitors accessed our site  
>  c) The pages visitors access  
>  d) The internet address of the website from which visitors linked to our site  
>  e) The e-mail addresses of visitors only when provided, for the purpose of sending information regarding new additions or updates to MMF! We do not share or sell our e-mail list ever.

This information is categorized and stored. It cannot be used to personally identify visitors. 

Third Party Ads and Product Images  
MMF! (Wave Music, LLC) uses third-party companies to serve text/image ads (Google, InfoLinks) and affiliate links/product images (SheetMusicPlus/Amazon) to support this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this website, their website, and other websites in order to present goods and services of interest to you. 

> a) Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
>  b) Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.  
>  c) Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
>  d) Third party vendors may or may not collect information about each website user. Websites will often send your computer a "cookie." A cookie is a small data file that is stored on your hard drive. They are most often used to enhance your website visitor experience. Modern browsers typically allow the users to decide whether to accept cookies, but rejection makes some websites unusable. Users assume responsibility for understanding the privacy policy of theses vendor sites. 

**Objectionable Ads**  
From time to time objectionable ads are served to our site. If you come across one, please contact us with information about the ad, including the company and product advertised. Together we can keep MakingMusicFun.net a safe and enjoyable resource for everyone.

Sign up to receive the MakingMusicFun.net Newsletter so you don't miss a thing!
